it is now 24 hours since the already
legendary Trump Kim summit frankly I'm
still buzzing and not just because my
phone's on silent and I have a debt
collector hounding me about my impounded
flamethrower
no no I'm also buzzing because there
were so many exciting moments yesterday
they got overshadowed by Trump's big win
and here to help me go over them citizen
journalists kobe libby and aaron jackson
guys welcome the other dust has settled
we can relax a little and let our hair
down oh that is better okay now in a
word how would you describe the summit
yesterday
I'd say historic like the launch of the
Titanic but without the shipwreck and
I'd say profoundly emotional like the
movie Titanic but without the Billy Zane
yes No
Cove it what moment really stood out to
you three words Dennis Rodman a very
strange twist in this story so Dennis
Rodman arrived in Singapore dr. Kim
hyun-jung
and an administration over there five
years ago and he sat down and asked me
hey Dennis I would like to ask you three
things if you go back to tell the
president United States these three
things and I would be willing to talk to
him and Obama didn't even give me the
time of day
he didn't give Dennis Rodman the time of
day
Obama wasted months talking to experts
on the history of the Korean Peninsula
Dennis Rodman could have given him 45
breathtaking minutes about the time he
and Kim went go-karting over peasants
now in spite of Dennis Robins obvious
expertise I know what you're thinking
why would Trump bring an NBA player with
him to Singapore answer he didn't Dennis
Rodman's trip was actually sponsored by
a cryptocurrency company called pot coin
here's Dennis Rodman walking with either
a senior executive from the company or
turtle from Entourage I bet you brought
this up Kobe so what what is pot coil
pot coin is a cryptocurrency
specifically designed to buy and sell
marijuana not to be confused with coin
pop the jar where I keep my change which
so far only has one investor is it me
it's you and to be clear we're still
talking about the North Korea summit
believe it or not we are you see even
though pot coin paid for Dennis Rodman's
trip to Singapore Trump valued his
contribution so much that Dennis Rodman
got a White House thank-you call which
makes sense because Republicans have a
long tradition of including NBA players
in diplomacy when Reagan visited Berlin
in 87 you know who was right there
beside him Boston Celtic Kevin McHale up
I believe the famous quote is mr.
Gorbachev tear down this wall and mr.
Mikhail
I can see your scrotum dipping out from
those shorts can I just add something
first of all great summary I didn't
understand a word of it but personally
I'm more interested in the human aspect
of this thing look at the human rights
aspect know the human interest aspect
the heart the drama and Dennis Rodman's
emotional thank yous some people yeah go
ahead let me ask you something you don't
go on a whole tour about it but thinking
Chuck Daly I'm taking Phil Jackson take
a Jeannie bus Eddie vetted approach
they're gonna take my kids they still
with me at all these years oh my god so
moving I'm not exactly sure what he's
talking about or why but it feels like
he just want a championship or an Oscar
and Pearl Jam is somehow involved I mean
I love North Korea now I heard Jeremy
spoke at the summit today okay no one
actually knows Pearl Jam references
Jordan but you know who really lit up
hearts this weekend Ivanka in response
to her daddy's critics Ivanka tweeted
those who say it cannot be done should
not interrupt those doing it Chinese
proverb incredible Ivanka's tweets pack
all the inspirational punch of a wrist
tattoo that says just breathe and to be
honest I'm pretty impressed that she
knows a Chinese proverb well admittedly
I guess in China people were baffled
with some calling it a fake proverb and
in fact it turned out was not China but
who knows more about Chinese culture
actual Chinese people or Ivanka whose
clothing line was once manufactured in
factories where real Chinese people
claimed they were actually abuse oh hey
man gents look we need to wrap this up
so real quick what do you hope to see in
future Trump Kim summits less research
more coin pocket
sorry pot coin yes and I'll just say
nine words Eric Trump haiku baby amazing
work as always guys the fight continues
opposers are there any three words more
exciting than click and subscribe
yes Hillary shot Lincoln subscribe now
and find out the truth they don't want
you to know and by day I mean losers
looking for YouTube handouts without
clicking subscribe do it